# **OLEG SHEPELEV**

## 106A Kabilov Street Kazakhstan Almaty +7-777-376-66-62

olegashepelev@gmail.com

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

2021 – 2022 WEB DEVELOPER, UDEMY

**REMOTE** 

**2019 FROM MARCH TO OCTOBER WEB DEVELOPER,** ATTRACTOR SCHOOL

**REMOTE** 

## BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY,

KAZAKHSTAN INSTITUTE OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES AND MANAGEMENT

KAZAKHSTAN, ALMATY

## COMPUTER DEVICE MAINTENANCE TECHNICIAN,

PROFESSIOANL LYCEUM Nº1

KAZAKHSTAN, ALMATY

## **EXPERIENCE**

2021-PRESENT

WEB DEVELOPER, PROJECT WORK

REMOTE

- www.glampings.kz current project.
- Used technologies: React, Redux, TypeScript, antDesign, SCSS, AJAX, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB

#### **2019 MARCH-OCTOBER**

#### WEB DEVELOPER. ATTRACTOR SCHOOL

REMOTELY IN THE FRAMEWORK OF TRAINING IN THE COURSES

- HTML/CSS/SCSS/BEM adaptive mobile layout, using Flex-box/Grid
- JavaScript > ES6/TypeScript
- jQuery
- React/Redux
- GIT
- AJAX
- Bootstrap/antDesign/Material-UI

#### 2006-PRESENT

## **PURCHASING MANAGER,**

#### LLP MELOMAN-HOME-VIDEO

#### KAZAKHSTAN, ALMATY

- In this company I started working as a sales consultant in a retail chain of stores.
- Purchase of products to the Microsoft Dynamics Axapta database.
- Training of junior employees in procurement.
- Control over the correct filling of all data for the purchase.
- Correction of miss-grading writing of defective goods and shortages.
- Adding new items to the database.
- Entering new overheads into the database.
- Advised accounting departments and capitalists department.
- I taught the employees of the accounting department to enter new names into the database, correctly create and distribute purchases, write off defective goods and shortages, and make returns based on purchases.
- Established the process of purchasing goods before they arrive at the warehouse.
- Implemented a business process for automating the procurement department.

#### 2004-2006

## PC OPERATOR, LLP CENTRAL HOUSE OF ACCOUNTANTS

KAZAKHSTAN, ALMATY

- Typing, printing, copying on a copier.
- Sale of computer components and accessories.
- Installation of software at the request of customers.
- Delivery of office supplies.

## **ABOUT ME**

I'VE BEEN DEVELOPING FOR ABOUT 2 YEARS.

BASIC KNOWLEDGE OF MONGODB, MONGOOSE, EXPRESS.JS, NODE.JS, AJAX. SKILLS IN USING HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, SASS, JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT, JQUERY, REACT, REDUX, GIT, BOOTSTRAP, ANTDESIGN, FIGMA.

ADAPTIVE LAYOUT SKILLS ACCORDING TO BEM METHODOLOGY.

KNOWLEDGE OF ENGLISH LEVEL B2.

## SKILLS

- Quickly learn everything new.
- Node JS, MongoDB
- React JS, HTML, CSS, SASS, JS
- WebStorm, Visual Studio Code
- Responsible
- Plan, organize, direct, control and evaluate daily operations
- Communicable
- Punctual
- Orderly
- MS Office
- MS Dynamics Axapta

# **ACTIVITIES**

I like playing basketball, watching hockey, going to the mountains, hiking, swimming, sunbathing, push-ups, pull-ups, travelling. I like watching a movie both in the cinema and at home. I often play board games.